With the help of Yukari Zou and Gero Longest Raku, we bring you another installment from Gero.
Team Shachi no Hachiman Gakuen
Yay!
I'm Yuuki Kogure and Haruna Sakamoto of Team Shachi!
We are here at Gerocchi again today as the Yuzo and Haruna pair!
Yay!
We've been looking for a little bit of fun in the city
as we stroll around town.
We would like to go deeper into the charms of Gerosee!
Please enjoy to the end!
I don't know what to do.
Please enjoy to the end.
Suddenly I'm not so sure.
Let's have fun.
I'm off.
Kinkong kankong!
So, this trip is all about looking for "Ei Ei" (reflection).
There are a lot of really cool spots in the cityscape.
I'd like to take a side trip while looking for natural beauty.
This is also "Ei Ei", isn't it?
Japan's Three Famous Lines
Where are the three most famous train lines in Japan?
Geroike and Kusatsu Onsen...
A-ha-ha-ha!
Ahimonsen
Correct answer
I cheated like crazy!
I'll keep the yuzuki too.
I took it a while ago.
I'll take it.
Here you go. Cheese.
Onsen, we have a song called Yu
Hot water, hot water, hot water
It's very nice. Thank you.
It's choreographed with hot water in mind.
Hot water, hot water, hot water.
This one's doubled, too.
It's double this way, too.
It's definitely twice as big.
Double discovery!
I didn't know it was a sensor.
Double it!
Do you see this on Instagram a lot?
It looks like a tower.
Is it?
So, Shimono Onsen is already popular.
It's very popular, but...
I wonder if this is it.
While we're waiting, let's take a look at the view from here.
Is this where you went earlier?
Where we just went.
We just went there... right over there.
Oh, yeah.
That's where we shot the opening.
Thank you, Mr. Resort.
thank you so much for your help
Thank you so much.
for letting us stay here.
Thank you very much.
YUKAI RESORT
I'm looking forward to it!
I'm looking forward to the hot springs and the food.
You're already having so much fun, aren't you?
I'm having so much fun!
We're going on a school trip, but we're not the same age as we would be if it were a real school trip.
If we were going on a real school trip, we wouldn't be the same age.
I see.
It's strange, isn't it?
Yeah, we're not the same age.
But we're members, so it's possible.
Then take a picture.
Wow!
Can you use that camera with a normal camera?
Oh, wait, that's great!
That's a cool way to take pictures.
Thank you very much.
Bye.
Definitely bi.
Gero Hot Springs
This is bi.This is bi.
It's my first post on instagram.
Thank you.
Hmm?
What? What? It says something.
I can't read it.
"White Foot Bath.
White-footed?
Eagle?
That's an eagle.
That's me.
No, it's not.
Tong.
No, it's me.
A hawk?
A hawk!
Eagle?
Egret?
If no one knows what it is, don't do it.
Come on, someone has to get it right.
Check it out.
I'll look into it.
Do it.
You know what's handy nowadays? You take a picture of it.
Gentlemen!
Let's go.
Here we go.
Take a picture, right?
You take a picture, and then you just click here, right?
See?
You can make a copy.
Oh, wow.
I'll copy it and look it up.
Search, search, search.
How to read
~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~
~~~~~~~~~~~~~
Oh!
It's full of them. Romanesque buildings?
Tell me, is that where we were?
What? That was just there!
What? That's where we were!
Let's go back.
Romanesque building is a hot spring? It's a public bathhouse with a history dating back to the Taisho era.
Wait a minute. It's like a puzzle game.
That's where we were!
Shall we go?
Well, maybe we can figure it out if we go back there.
Maybe there's a clue there.
I'm waiting for the pound to move.
This is the building, right?
Yeah, that's it. That's it.
I don't get it.
I don't know.
You want to go inside?
Sure. Or should I ask?
It's written, it's written, it's written, it's written...
Shira, what kind of hot water is it?
Excuse me.
Hello.
Hello. Excuse me.
I was just looking at the name of this hot spring from outside.
We didn't know how to read it.
What kind of hot water is it?
It's "Shirasagi no Yu
Shirasagi no Yu
That's how you write it, isn't it?
Why Shirasagi?
Because my feet hurt.
It was a hot spring that healed my injury.
It was the hot spring that gave it to him.
Then... are you saying...
Are all the white birds and things like that written in the book "Shirahagi"?
Shirasagi.
Oh, a white-winged egret?
I see.
I'm sorry. Thank you very much.
Idols.Idol.
Idol.
My name is Team Orca. Nice to meet you.
What's your team?
Team Shachi.
Aren't you Shachiko?
It was the President's son.
You're the president of the team?
Yes, sir.
Oh, my God.
Isn't that amazing?
Is that a spanker?
Pusher?
Gero is one of the three most famous boats in Japan.
Shirasagi soaked in it.
He got rid of his fatigue...
It healed his leg.
From the fact that his legs were healed
Shirasagi is also very important
And from the word "vomit"...
And lots of frogs.
That's great!
So many wonderful things
We're learning
We're learning... it's a school... this program...
After this, we're going to the inn.
We're going to the inn.
It's a solo episode, so please watch it!
Please watch it!
Bye-bye!
It's time for Killer Whale News!
Here is our latest news!
We will be performing at the Spring Stardust Special Live in Kijima Kogen 2023 on April 30th at Kijima Kogen Park!
We've been wanting to perform at Kijima Kogen Park for a long time!
I've always wanted to do that!
We do a lot of live shows in Kyushu.
Basho has always said that Kijima Kogen is really good!
As a fellow Stardust Stapler, I've been told about it.
But this time, we were able to do a live show with another Stardust Stapler friend, Chotoki Meki Propaganda Club!
I'm so excited to be able to perform with my fellow Stardust Stapler, Tokisen-chan!
I'm so excited!
We're all so excited to be a part of it!
And we're looking forward to seeing what kind of collaborations you fans will come up with.
Please come and join us!
We look forward to seeing you there!
February 30th.
And we will be performing as SHACHI Flavor in Tokyo.
SHACHI Flavor will be performing in Tokyo!
The date is May 18!
We will be performing at Shinjuku Blaze in Tokyo.
We have already finished the Nagoya show.
I think everyone's expectations are even higher now.
We will give you a great live performance that will surpass the Nagoya show.
Please come and visit us!
We look forward to seeing you there!
And on July 22nd, we will be dancing the SHACHI summer at Nagoya Castle!
Yay!
It's no exaggeration to say that this will be our biggest show of the year!
We're going to put everything we have into it this year!
I'm going to put everything on it!
The first half of the year and the second half of the year
I'm going to put it all on!
So please put your all into it!
I'm sure you'll find someone like you are right now.
And flash it to a hundred of your friends.
Sign up now!
We look forward to working with you.
We'll be waiting for you!
That's all for now, SHACHI NEWS!
Bye bye!